Mai Houa Vue

PROFILE

Front-End developer with insight into community wants and needs due to community outreach experience, wanting to build websites for UX marketing purposes. A self-motivated and ambitious individual with knowledge of HTML5, CSS JavaScript, Jquery and responsive web applications.

EDUCATION

University of Wisconsin Extended Campus Coding
Bootcamp - October 2019-current

University of Wisconsin-Madison- Graduate of 2013 Bachelor of Arts- Zoology, Certificate in Global Health

EXPERIENCE

Community Health Services Representative II

Managed Health Services-WI

- Training staff on variety of work tasks: call campaigns, administrative tasks, and other related activities
- Lead home visit campaigns
- Writing up work processes for internal tasks and outreach campaigns

MemberConnections Representative I

November 2014 - April 2017

April 2017 - current

Managed Health Services-WI

- Home visits to assess health needs through assessments, deliver health plan phones, and addressing care gaps
- Outbound call campaigns
- Attending community events to represent health plan

Contact

608-556-3292

mhvue4@gmail.com

2597 N. Murray Ave. Apt 2 Milwaukee. WI 53211

References

Teresa Covi

Supervisor Community Health Services Representative Managed Health Services-WI 414-242-9049

Lakeeta Watts

Community Health Worker Coordinator UniteMKE 262-505-7811

Portfolio

mhvue.github.io/updated_portfolio